Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
In an effort to undo the curse that Venno placed on Asta's arms,
our friends headed to the Forest of Witches to speak to the Queen.
Once there, they found Vanessa in dire trouble.
She's got Vanessa!
Vanessa!
What do you think you're doing?
I don't care if you are the Queen or whatever, get your foot off our friend right now!
You dare barge into my home and address me that way?
What a foolish girl I've raised.
She told me she would become my slave and live out the rest of her days here.
All for restoring those silly arms of yours.
She really did that?
But just when they were about to battle the Queen and save their friend...
I didn't expect it to happen so soon.
New enemies descended upon the forest.
The Eye of the Midnight Sun.
Flame spirit magic.
Salamander's breath.
Recognizing the severity of the threat, the Queen of Witches restored Asta's arms in exchange for help against their common foe.
Oh yeah!
I am back in the game!
Get ready!
It's time to go!
Yeah!
Her superior healing magic made Asta even stronger than before.
And so, he began his battle against the vengeful Fauna.
I'll make sure this is the last time.
Keep on showing up!
And I'll just keep on fighting you off!
Let's go!
eins-
Now let's endune scene.
Now let's move forward.
Let's win another scene!
I'm not for you now
I'm still on my own
I'm on my own
I'll keep fighting you all forever
So bring it on
Again and again and again and again
Do you hear me?
Whatever you throw at me
I'm always gonna throw it right back at you
A hundred times over
Let's go!
I guess he must have built up a lot of energy
While his arms were out of commission
You're vile
But this time without a doubt
You'll die!
Here she comes!
Now flame spirit magic
Salamanders!
Talon!
The fire spirit salamander is believed to possess the greatest offensive strength among all four great nature spirits
What?
Seriously?
It's so powerful
The fire spirit salamander is believed to possess the greatest offensive strength among all four great nature spirits
We might as well be facing an entire nation's army
Amazing!
Spirits are mana made flesh
And Asta's anti-magic sword tears mana to pieces
Damn that was scary!
But it's really awesome too!
I want a salamander!
How can I get me one?
With Asta?
You're pretty good
But that Veto guy was a whole lot quicker on his feet than you are
Me and my team, we've got this
We might just win
Hmph
Honestly, watching you makes me feel downright silly for being scared
Okay
Why are these flames impossible to put out?
They just keep coming back
we've got this we might just win
honestly watching you makes me feel downright silly for being scared
why are these flames impossible to put out they just keep coming back
i guess i'm just wasting my magic power at this point
i'm worried i hope they'll be okay
how could you be so despicable i hate you
now counter-attack yeah sure
you know what i think we should have a little talk huh you've got to be kidding me
she's not someone to chit chat with you say that you hate us what the heck did we do to make you
that upset what's your beef with the clover kingdom can't you explain i mean how are we supposed to
understand one another if all we ever do is fight
ready to talk be quiet
what i tell you help me out here finral you got it
your old buddy feto that guy had it out for us too
we the eye of the midnight sun had golden dreams and bonds of blood
yes
and he was full of despair too
i want to know why help me to understand you
so
luct is that a human
yes
he's a good friend of mine
There's something very...mysterious about him.
I truly believe there will soon come a day when all of us can exist together in harmony.
Let's foster understanding. Your elvish mana really is a remarkable thing.
If we combine that with our own magic item technology, this land will be safer and more prosperous.
Let's all work together, hand in hand.
Congratulations to the happy couple!
I can sense that the mana has blessed our lives as well.
We're so happy to bring our new child into this world, and I know your kind is pleased to welcome it.
This little one here is our future. The bridge between elves and humankind.
It's the humans! They're attacking us!
Oh no! Please don't die!
Goodbye, dear.
Why, damn it!
He did this!
He's the only one that knows this place!
I knew it! That human betrayed all of us!
No!
You...
How could anyone trust your kind?
What's that magic?
There's so much hatred in me!
Do you really think you'll be able to do this?
No!
Do you really think you will be able to withstand it all?
She's got a third eye, too!
Whoa!
That thing is huge!
Now!
No!
That thing is huge now!
I've got you, Asta!
Here's a portal!
So not only has it gotten bigger, now it's using a new power, too?
It'd be nice to catch a break for once.
The flames of my hatred will burn you into oblivion!
Well, this is a pain. In that case, I'll just have to bust out my special move!
Oh, wow. That's no ordinary mage.
Hmm... I just thought of a great idea!
Come on! The Force of the Heat threw me back! I'll need some help to get close to her.
Vanessa, you doing okay?
Finral, how about you? Still hanging in there?
I think so. She's tricky.
It looks like she used her insane amount of magic power to generate a mana force field.
I'm having a really hard time creating my portals.
And the second I cast my thread magic, it burns right up!
This girl is untouchable!
So this is a spirit, huh?
It's like fighting a god incarnate!
You're done!
Here she comes!
Water creation magic!
You're done!
Here she comes!
Water creation magic!
Sea dragon's cradle!
The second I cast my thread magic, it burns right up!
This girl is untouchable!
So this is a spirit, huh?
It's like fighting a god incarnate!
You're done!
Here she comes!
Water creation magic!
Sea dragon's cradle!
What are you three doing?
Good thing I'm here!
Perfect timing!
What gives?
I've been putting out fires, but they keep coming back!
Time to address the source!
Yikes, I wasn't expecting something so scary!
Like I said, I'll just go ahead and knock this out real quick!
She's just who we needed!
Got that right!
Water beach fire!
The water's turning to steam!
Now flame spirit magic!
Salamander's talent!
Alright everyone, hang on tight!
That monster won't be easy to defeat!
Still, it's all up to me and my water magic!
I can do it!
I know I can!
I can! I can! I can! I can! I can!
Don't be stupid!
You were born defective and nothing's changed!
You'll lose now just like you've always lost before!
That attack of yours at the underwater temple?
A fluke that only worked because you let your emotions get the best of you!
Face it, you're nothing but a failure!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
They are right on useless!
You are strong!
Noelle! Listen to me, okay? You can do this! We can't fight those flames! It's up to you!
Come on, come on, come on!
What are you saying?
Does he have to be so loud? I can feel a headache coming on.
Um, Asta, I think you could keep it down.
You're a big bad magic knight now!
Hey, Mineral, why are you plugging your ears? Is the wind bothering you?
Noelle, you ready?
Yes.
Get it together. How many times has Asta given you the courage to fight?
You've got what it takes!
Like I need you to tell me, Dorksta! You just sit back and watch!
You've done your part! Now it's my turn to give you courage!
Here goes!
Get ready!
I only have enough power and reserve for one cast of Sea Dragon's Roar!
Everything is riding! On this single shot!
It's nothing but a failure! That's not me anymore!
Water creation magic! Sea Dragon's Roar!
You've shattered it! Begun!
Look out!
I'm not finished yet!
No way!
Amazing!
We're alive!
You must die! All of you!
Well, Asta! See? I bet you didn't know I was that powerful! Yay!
I did it! You crushed that thing!
Showed it what a real black bull can do! Way to go!
Way to go!
The salamander's down for the count thanks to Noelle's attack! It's now or never!
All right!
Asta!
Ready? Let's go!
Ready?
Okay! Finally time for my special move!
You will die! Mineral creation magic!
Mineral creation magic!
Wait, how would she use something besides flame magic?
That's so not fair!
Dispel!
Now flame recovery magic!
Activate Phoenix Robe!
And she can wield recovery spells, seriously?
Not cool!
I've seen that one before, too.
I knew it.
Hey! Flame Lady!
Do you happen to have a brother who's incredibly pale, has really spiky hair, and looks like he's never smiled before?
No!
It looks very calm and just as understandable as many of us!
one of you. I'm not getting through to her at all. Man, guess we'll just have to stop her with
my special move before she can finish healing herself. Yeah, and speaking of which, what exactly
is this new special move you're so excited about? I was wondering that too. I've been waiting for
you guys to ask me that. See, it goes like this. I hold both swords out in front of me, fly through
the air at super speed, and plunge them right into the enemy's magic. I call it... Is that even
possible? Wait, you mean it isn't? Maybe it wouldn't be if we weren't here. You're always
coming up with the craziest ideas. Let us give you a hand with that new move. It's like I
told you before, Asta. Friends help you overcome a fate you can't defeat on your own. We're
here for you. Your special move is gonna be incredible. Here we go. It's too late. You're
not killing anybody. You hear me? Bullthrust! We won! Alright! My special move totally kicked
Mr. Byte! Mr. Byte! It can't be. I failed.
Mr. Byte!
M
Hi!
Don't let up, still, wherebasun, don't wanna be like me
Oh you think...
Is there aこと?
Again and again!!
Bring it on! Again and again and again and again and again!!
I'll just keep fighting you off every single time,
time again and again and again! Try me!
Yeah, bring it on! Fishing over fisting over fisting!
I'll just keep leading you up every single time! Try me!
Yeah, bring it on! Soybean after fermented soybean!
I'll just keep slicing you up again and again, fermented soybeans!
My swords are covered in you now!
Wouldn't want to get stabbed by those things! Gross!
You did it, kiddo! You defeated Salamander!
Black Clover, page 60, defector's atonement!
No, Asta, it has nothing to do with toning your muscles!
The word is atonement, as in paying for your sins!